



hharan987@gmail.com



+65 97419348



linkedin.com/in/harihara-dhamodaran-335a4b1bb



stackoverflow.com/users/162 40306/harizh

SKILLS

REACT JS

NODE JS

EXPRESS JS

FLUTTER

AVAL

SPRING MVC

SPRING BOOT

JAVA SCRIPT

HTML

CSS

BOOTSTRAP

TAIL WIND CSS

BLOCK CHAIN / SMART CONTRACT

MYSQL

POSTGRESQL

MSSQL

MONGO DB

GRAPHOL

GIT/BITBUCKET

JIRA

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Tamil

Full Professional Proficiency

Japanese Elementary Proficiency

Harihara dhamodaran K

Full Stack Developer

An experienced software engineer with a 3.8 years of working experience as a full stack developer. Always focusing on new learnings and strict to code standards. Ability to handle multiple tasks and creative approach to problem solving.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MERN STACK DEVELOPER Keppel Corporation Limited

11/2022 - Present Singapore

- In keppel I Have been working on multiple projects from scratch. One project is Vessel crew management system and the other project is Rig Care management.
- Designing a high level user interface using react library with the help of HTML,CSS & REACT-BOOTSTRAP.
- Using react is design patterns with javascript to implement a reusable components.
- Using axios library for integrating a HTTP API.
- Using Express js server side framework to managing a backend route and business logics.
- Using Postgresql,MSSQL & stored procedures for performing CRUD operations on the database.
- Using NGINX & Load balancer for server hosting.
- Regularly participating code review with team to ensure code standards of both frontend and backend.

Contact: Manikandan B(Project manager) - +65 98522506

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Inforge Technologies Private Limited

04/2021 - 11/2022 Coimbatore/India

- In inforge I was worked on multiple projects with different programming languages.
- One project called calm in crisis developed using Flutter(UI SDK), Express JS(Backend framework) & graphQL(database). I have worked on both UI side as well as server side.
- Another project called AAJ which is a ERP for car auction company located in japan. This project was developed using JAVA(SPRING BOOT), HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JSP & MONGO DB.

Contact: Brindhan(Project Manager) - +91 9944955332

JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER

560 Degree Solutions

07/2020 - 04/2021 Trichy/India

- In 560, I was started my career as a Java developer using Spring MVC framework.
- As a junior developer, I had lot of experience of learning from the mistakes. Used those mistakes as a oppurtunity to learn more.
- Developed more than 30 API'S and followed spring mvc flow for code standard.
- Used MYSQL database for CRUD operations.

Contact: Ramesh(Project Manager) - +91 8870011560

EDUCATION

07/2014 - 05/2018

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE

Sevei Shanthi Matriculation Higher Secondary School

04/2012 - 04/2014

HSC

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

KSR Institute For Engineering And Technology

Namakkal/India

Trichy/India